{
    "questions":[{
        "question": "Which country won the first professional football world cup ?",
        "choice1": "Argentina",
        "choice2": "Germany",
        "choice3": "Uruguay",
        "choice4": "Netherlands",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Before the introduction of plastic helmets, what were they made out of in the NFL?",
        "choice1": "Latex",
        "choice2": "Leather",
        "choice3": "Steel",
        "choice4": "Cardboard",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In January of 2019, which NBA player broke Wilt Chamberlain's record of most consecutive games with a triple-double?",
        "choice1": "Russell Westbrook",
        "choice2": "Stephen Curry",
        "choice3": "Kobe Bryant",
        "choice4": "James Harden",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who defeated Rafael Nadal at the 2016 men's singles U.S. Open tournament?",
        "choice1": "Tiger Woods",
        "choice2": "Roger Federer",
        "choice3": "Novak Djokovic",
        "choice4": "Lucas Pouille",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The ground on which the game of golf is played is known as ?",
        "choice1": "Golf Land",
        "choice2": "Green Land",
        "choice3": "Golf Pit",
        "choice4": "Golf course",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League ?",
        "choice1": "Mohammed Salah",
        "choice2": "Thierry Henry",
        "choice3": "Sadio Mane",
        "choice4": "Didier Drogba",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of theses players did not share the Premier League Golden Boot in 2018-19 ?",
        "choice1": "Sadio Mane",
        "choice2": "Harry Kane",
        "choice3": "Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang",
        "choice4": "Mohammed Salah",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you name the former Germany international who went on to become a professional wrestler in the WWE ?",
        "choice1": "Phillip Wiese",
        "choice2": "Tim Wiese",
        "choice3": "Matt Wiese",
        "choice4": "David Dunker",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Messi famously retired from international duty in which year before reversing his decision ?",
        "choice1": "2017",
        "choice2": "2018",
        "choice3": "2015",
        "choice4": "2016",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which German multinational sportswear company is Messi an ambassador for ?",
        "choice1": "Nike",
        "choice2": "Adidas",
        "choice3": "Jaguar",
        "choice4": "Zara",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which player holds the record for most Champions League winners' medals ?",
        "choice1": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "choice2": "Raul",
        "choice3": "Francesco Gento",
        "choice4": "Sergio Ramos",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "In which year was the first European Championship held ?",
        "choice1": "1964",
        "choice2": "1963",
        "choice3": "1962",
        "choice4": "1960",
        "answer": 4
    }



]
}